Now for the big quiz. In all seriousness, this is the most
现在我们来一个终极测试。 只是一个非常严肃，而且
complicated exercise I've given you so far this lesson. I want you
很复杂的锻炼，需要你所学的所有只是。 你要做的就是
to implement the details view using the cursor loader and multiple text view
去使用cusor loader 和 multiple text view 去完成details view
widgets. And I've got some hints for you. Use loaders
我已经给你很多的线索啦。 请使用loaders
not adapters. What does this mean? Well, it makes sense. Your detail
而不是adapters. 这意味着什么？ 呵呵， 这意味着你的detail
view does not contain a list so you don't
view 不能包涵一个列表从而你不需要去
need to use an adapter, but you can still
使用一个adapter,不过你依然需要使用
use the loader pattern. The loader pattern will automatically
一个loader pattern. 这个loader pattern 将会自动的
observe for changes in the URI with a CursorLoader. The
观察所有在URI里Cursorloader的变化。
second thing you want to do is pass the date
第二， 你需要做的是输入你想要
into your intent. The date is the important thing to
的日期。这个日期将会是一个非常重要的
the detail you need to have passed into it
细节数据党你需要输入的时候会提供
to properly query the content provider. Now remember, you can
一个content provider 的查询。 好的，现在你要记住， 你可以
actually get the current location settings from the utility function. So
从utility 函数中拿到现在的位置设置。 这就是
all you really need is the date. I hope that helps.
你全部所需要的数据， 我希望这些线索能帮到你。